I
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): would think since you disagree with the Chinese way of life, which is pretty civilized in a lot of ways, but the one way in which it's barbaric is that it grants its citizens no real rights. And so I would think that you would be very worried about aping their system, which we are now doing. They have total surveillance. It's a panopticon in China. We should create our own. Let's take 40,000 acres in Utah and make it possible for the government to know where you are at all times and what you're thinking, listening to you on your phone. Like, we have that.
Speaker 2: You have to choose the less of two evils in your scenario. And I'm telling you, what
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): you should do is say, I want
Kevin O'Leary
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): to succeed. I want him to beat the Chinese and compute power. Then use the laws of the United States to make sure that you keep that compute power in check. To not have it available, to put down my shovel, I don't think people want me to do that. Even the people in Box Elder, the majority of them want me to hold my shovel and start digging. There
Speaker 4: was a referendum among citizens? Three to zero. Zero.
Speaker 4: The commissioners of the county
Speaker 5: said we want to be part of this.
Speaker 6: So three people voted, the people of the county.
Speaker 5: They're elected officials. That's
Speaker 7: how you do it. How hard is it
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): for Kevin O'Leary and Amazon and Microsoft and Google to subvert
Speaker 8: three county commissioners in rural Utah?
Speaker 5: They asked us to come. They asked us to bring $15 billion. Amazon, Google, and Kevin
Speaker 9: O'Leary got three county commissioners in rural Utah on their side. Good
work